Guide to the Tamiment Library Web Archive (Labor and the Left): Labor Unions and Organizations (U.S.) TAM.507
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archive
Tamiment Library Web Archive (Labor and the Left): Labor Unions and Organizations (U.S.)
2007-
TAM.507
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archive
0.0010 linear feet (1+ websites; i.e., a collection of websites that grows on an ongoing basis)
The Tamiment Library Web Archive (Labor and the Left): Alternative Mass Media, was created with the Web Archiving Service from the California Digital Library. The Web Archiving Service was made possible with support from the National Digital Information and Infrastructure Preservation Program and the University of California, as part of a project to preserve born-digital political communication. The Tamiment Library creates topically based archives of websites documenting labor and left activity, principally that based in the United States. The collection contains periodically archived websites of New York City metropolitan area Labor Unions, especially those whose records are held by the Tamiment Library's Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives (designated by the New York City Central Labor Council as the official repository for their member unions' records), websites of selected national labor unions, and websites of labor movement related organizations, e.g. organizations that support the goals/activity of organized labor and social and economic justice for working people, and websites that promote democracy within labor unions. NOTE: For technical, privacy and other reasons, archived websites may not be exact copies of the original website at the time of the web crawl. Note: if a link does not work, click on the TITLE of this archive (in the "Description" section at the beginning of the finding aid) to access the archive, then use the site list to select the web site(s) you wish to view.
Tamiment Library.
Scope and Contents note
Contains periodically archived websites of New York City metropolitan area Labor Unions, especially those whose records are held by the Tamiment Library's Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives (designated by the New York City Central Labor Council as the official repository for their member unions' records). Also contains websites of selected national labor unions; websites of labor movement related organizations, e.g. organizations that support the goals/activity of organized labor and social and economic justice for working people; and websites that promote democracy within labor unions. NOTE: For technical, privacy and other reasons, archived websites may not be exact copies of the original website at the time of the web crawl.
Note: if a link does not work, click on the TITLE of this archive (in the "Description" section at the beginning of the finding aid) to access the archive, then use the site list to select the web site(s) you wish to view.
Historical/Biographical Note
The Tamiment Library Web Archive (Labor and the Left): Labor unions and Organizations (U.S.), was created with the Web Archiving Service from the California Digital Library. This service employs open source web archiving utilities developed by Internet Archive with the support of the The International Internet Preservation Consortium. The Web Archiving Service was made possible with support from the National Digital Information and Infrastructure Preservation Program and the University of California, as part of a project to preserve born-digital political communication. The role of the Tamiment Library during this project and thereafter was/is to create topically based archives of websites documenting contemporary and ongoing labor and left activity, principally that based in the United States.
Related Material at the Tamiment Library/Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
A list of related web archives, whose ns2:titles all begin with the prefix "Tamiment Library Web Archive (Labor and the Left)," can be found at the website Web Archives from New York University Libraries.
Access Restrictions
Open for research without restrictions.
Arrangement
Websites arranged alphabetically.
AFL-CIO. New York City Central Labor Council.; Labor movement |z United States.; Labor union democracy |z New York (State) |z New York.; Labor union democracy |z United States.; Labor unions |z New York (State); Labor unions |z New York (State) |z New York.; Working class |z United States
- Labor Unions and Organizations (U.S.) Web Archive
  - 1199SEIU United Healthcare Workers East, 6/16/2010-
  - Actors' Equity Association, 09/23/2007-
  - Actors' Fund of America, 09/23/2007-
  - AFL-CIO New York City Central Labor Council, 09/24/2007-
  - AFL-CIO Working Families Vote 2008, 08/16/2009-3/8/2010
  - AFL-CIO.org, 12/02/2009-
  - Air Line Pilots Association (ALPA), 12/3/2009-
  - Albert Shanker Institute, 07/26/2009-
  - Amalgamated Transit Union (ATU), 12/11/2009-
  - American Federation of Government Employees (AFGE), 12/7/2009-
  - American Federation of Musicians, Local 802, 09/23/2007-
  - American Federation of Musicians of the United States and Canada (AFM), 12/3/2009-
  - American Federation of School Administrators (AFSA), 12/3/2009-
  - American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees (AFSCME), 12/2/2009-
  - American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees (AFSCME) District Council 37 (New York, N.Y.), 09/24/07-
  - American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees (AFSCME) Local 1930 (New York, N.Y.), 09/24/2007-
  - American Federation of Teachers (AFT), 12/2/2009-
  - American Federation of Television and Radio Artists, 09/23/2007-7/11/2012
  - American Guild of Musical Artists, 11/21/2008-
  - American Guild of Variety Artists, 4/23/2012-
  - American Postal Workers Union (APWU), 12/3/2009-
  - American Rights at Work, 09/24/2007-
  - Association for Union Democracy, 02/07/2007-
  - Association of Flight Attendants (AFA-CWA), 12/3/2009-
  - Bakery, Confectionery, Tobacco Workers and Grain Millers International Union (BCTGM), 12/3/2009-
  - Bitch Magazine, 11/9/2009-
  - Black Workers for Justice, 5/8/2011-
  - Brandworkers International, 5/12/2012-
  - Bread and Roses Cultural Project, 8/8/2009
  - Brotherhood of Railroad Signalmen (BRS), 12/3/2009-
  - Building Bridges Radio: Your Community & Labor Report, 08/08/2009-
  - Building Trades Employers Association of the City of New York, 02/01/2009-
  - California Nurses Association/National Nurses Organizing Committee (CNA/NNOC), 12/3/2009-12/27/2011
  - Center for Labor Renewal, 5/5/2011-
  - Center for Study of Working Class Life, 5/3/2011-
  - Change to Win, 12/2/2009-
  - Chinese Staff Workers Association, 09/25/07-
  - Civil Service Merit Council, 02/04/2009-3/04/2009
  - Civil Service Technical Guild, Local 375, DC 37, AFSCME - AFL-CIO, 09/24/2007-
  - Coalition of Black Trade Unionists, 09/24/07-
  - Coalition of Graduate Employee Unions, 7/9/2011-
  - Coalition of Labor Union Women, 09/23/2007-
  - Committee for Free Trade Unionism, 09/17/2009-
  - Communications Workers of America, 09/24/2007-
  - Communications Workers of America. District 1, 09/24/2007-
  - Communications Workers of America. District 2, 03/02/2009-
  - Communications Workers of America. Local 1032, 02/26/2009-
  - Communications Workers of America. Local 1101, 02/27/2009-
  - Communications Workers of America. Local 1103, 03/03/2009-
  - Communications Workers of America. Local 1150, 02/25/2009-
  - Communications Workers of America, Local 1153, 02/26/2009-
  - Communications Workers of America, Local 1180, 09/24/2007-
  - Cyberunions, 11/9/2011-
  - David Bacon Photographs & Stories, 09/24/2007-
  - Domestic Workers United, 5/4/2011-
  - Employee Free Choice Act Now!, 12/23/2008-12/24/2010
  - Excluded Workers Congress, 10/18/2011-
  - Farm Labor Organizing Committee (FLOC), 12/3/2009-
  - Glass, Molders, Pottery, Plastics and Allied Workers International Union (GMP), 12/3/2009-
  - Guerrilla News Network, 02/02/2009-
  - Industrial Workers of the World, 02/07/2007-
  - International Alliance of Theatrical and Stage Employees, Local 52, 02/08/2009-
  - International Alliance of Theatrical Stage Employees, Moving Picture Technicians, Artists and Allied Crafts of the United States, Its Territories and Canada, 12/3/2009-
  - International Association of Bridge, Structural, Ornamental and Reinforcing Iron Workers (Ironworkers), 12/6/2009-
  - International Association of Fire Fighters (IAFF), 12/10/2009-
  - International Association of Heat and Frost Insulators and Allied Workers, 12/3/2009-
  - International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers (IAM), 12/3/2009-
  - International Brotherhood of Boilermakers, Iron Ship Builders, Blacksmiths, Forgers and Helpers, 12/3/2009-
  - International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers (IBEW), 12/3/2009-
  - International Brotherhood of Painters and Allied Trades. Painters District Council 9 of New York City, 09/24/07-
  - International Brotherhood of Teamsters (IBT), 12/2/2009-
  - International Federation of Professional and Technical Engineers (IFPTE), 12/3/2009-
  - International Labor Communications Association, 02/07/2007-
  - International Longshore and Warehouse Union (ILWU), 12/3/2009-
  - International Longshoremen's Association (ILA), 12/3/2009-
  - International Union of Bricklayers and Allied Craftworkers (BAC), 12/3/2009-
  - International Union of Bricklayers and Allied Craftworkers. Local 7 (New York and New Jersey), 05/03/2009-
  - International Union of Elevator Constructors (IUEC), 12/3/2009-
  - International Union of Operating Engineers (IUOE), 12/3/2009-
  - International Union of Painters and Allied Trades, 4/25/2012-
  - International Union of Police Associations (IUPA), 12/4/2009-
  - International Union, United Automobile, Aerospace and Agricultural Implement Workers of America (UAW) Local 2110, 03/21/2009-
  - International Union, United Automobile, Aerospace and Agricultural Implement Workers of America (UAW), 09/24/2007-
  - Jewish Labor Committee, 03/19/2009-
  - Jobs With Justice, 02/07/2007-
  - Labor and Working Class History Association, 10/14/2009-
  - Labor Arts, 09/24/2007-
  - Labor Community Strategy Center, 5/5/2011-
  - Labor Express, 11/10/2011-
  - Labor Heritage Foundation, 09/24/2007-
  - Labor History Links Home Page, 10/22/2011-
  - Labor Network for Sustainability, 5/12/2012-
  - Labor Notes, 02/07/2007-
  - Labor Press, 10/13/2009-
  - LaborBeat.org, 02/07/2007-
  - Laborers' International Union of North America, 4/28/2012-
  - LaborNet (U.S.), 02/07/2007-
  - LaborTech, 11/17/2010-
  - Manumit School (1924-1957), 09/01/2009-
  - Marine Engineers' Beneficial Association (MEBA), 12/09/2009-
  - Metro New York Labor Communications Council, 5/12/2010-
  - Million Worker March Movement, 7/20/2011-
  - National Air Traffic Controllers Association (NATCA), 12/4/2009-
  - National Association of Broadcast Employees and Technicians: The Broadcasting and Cable Television Workers Sector of the Communications Workers of America, 03/13/2009-
  - National Association of Letter Carriers (NALC), 12/3/2009-
  - National Domestic Workers Alliance, 10/26/2011-
  - National Education Association, 12/2/2009-
  - National Guestworker Alliance, 5/11/2012-
  - National Labor College, 5/12/2012-
  - National Mobilization Against Sweatshops, 09/25/2007-
  - National Nurses United, 1/14/2009-
  - National Organization of Legal Services Workers (NOLSW), UAW Local 2320, 01/28/2009-
  - National Postal Mail Handlers Union, 4/25/2012-
  - New York Building Congress, 03/13/2009-
  - New York Chapter of the National Writers Union, Local 1981, 02/06/2009-
  - New York Committee for Occupational Safety and Health, 02/07/07-
  - New York Hotel and Motel Trades Council, 03/13/2009
  - New York Labor History Association, 04/30/09
  - New York State AFL-CIO, 09/24/2007-
  - New York State Public Employees Federation, 11/05/2011-
  - New York Taxi Workers Alliance
  - Newspaper Guild of New York, Local 3, 02/05/2009-
  - Office and Professional Employees International Union (OPEIU), 12/3/2009-
  - Operative Plasterers' and Cement Masons' International Association of the United States and Canada (OP&CMIA), 12/7/2009-
  - Professional Aviation Safety Specialists (PASS), 12/3/2009-
  - Professional Staff Congress/City University of New York, 09/24/2007-
  - Progressive Librarians Guild, 11/24/2008-
  - Radicals at Work, 4/1/2011-
  - Restaurant Opportunities Centers United, 7/4/2011-
  - Retail, Wholesale, and Department Store Union. Local 1-S Department Store Workers Union, 03/16/09-
  - Screen Actors Guild (SAG), 12/3/2009-9/19/2012
  - Screen Actors Guild, New York Branch, 03/10/2009-
  - Seafarers International Union, 4/27/2012-
  - Service Employees International Union (SEIU), 12/2/2009-
  - Sheet Metal Workers International Association (SMWIA), 12/7/2009-
  - Sheet Metal Workers International Association, Local 137, 03/10/2009-
  - Social Service Employees Union Local 371, 09/24/2007-
  - Starbucks Workers Union (IWW), 09/25/2007-
  - Stella Doro Strike 2008, 08/15/2009-5/5/2011
  - Street Vendors Mobilizing and Organizing in Solidarity, 5/6/2012-
  - Teamsters for a Democratic Union, 02/07/2007-
  - The Wage Project, 11/9/2009-
  - Transport Workers Union of America, 09/24/2007-
  - Transport Workers Union of America. Local 100, 09/24/2007-
  - UFT Alliance of Charter Teachers & Staff, 11/9/2011-
  - Union Democracy Review, 02/07/2007-
  - Union Jobs Clearinghouse, 09/26/2007-
  - Union Label, 5/14/2012-
  - Union of Clerical, Administrative & Technical Staff at NYU, Local 3882, NYSUT, AFT, AFL-CIO, 09/24/2007-
  - Union Songs, 08/10/2009-
  - UnionBook, 07/29/2009-
  - Unite Here (Organization), 09/23/2007-
  - United American Nurses (UAN), 12/7/2009-9/6/2011
  - United Association for Labor Education, 08/08/2009-
  - United Association of Journeymen and Apprentices of the Plumbing and Pipe Fitting Industry of the United States and Canada (UA), 1/7/2010-
  - United Brotherhood of Carpenters, 4/28/2012-
  - United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America: Cabinetmakers Local 2090, 03/20/2009-
  - United Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers of America (UE), 5/13/2012-
  - United Farm Workers of America, 12/2/2009-
  - United Federation of Teachers, 09/24/2007-
  - United Food and Commercial Workers International Union (UFCW), 12/2/2009-
  - United Mine Workers of America (UMWA), 12/7/2009-
  - United Steel, Paper and forestry, Rubber, Manufacturing, Energy, Allied Industrial & Service Workers International Union (USW), 12/7/2009-
  - United Transportation Union (UTU), 12/7/2009-
  - United Union of Roofers, Waterproofers and Allied Workers (Roofers and Waterproofers), 12/7/2009-
  - UPPNET, 8/8/2009-
  - US Federation of Worker Cooperatives, 11/4/2011-
  - US Labor Against the War, 09/24/07-
  - Utility Workers Union of America, Local 1-2, 02/19/09
  - Utility Workers Union of America (UWUA), 12/7/2009-
  - Vermont Workers' Center, 5/15/2011-
  - Wobbly City: Newsletter of the NYC Branch (IWW), 07/26/2009-
  - Women on the Job, 03/09/2009-
  - Working America, 10/23/2011-
  - Working-Class Perspectives, 1/19/2010-
  - Working Life, 09/24/2007-
  - Writers Guild of America, East Inc. (WGAE), 12/7/2009-